Hi, friends!
Let's go back in time!
Long, long ago, there were dinosaurs.
Listen!
Stomp, stomp!
Look!
A giant dinosaur is coming!
It is a T. rex!
Its long name is Tyrannosaurus rex.
It lives in North America.
T. rex is very big.
It is as long as a bus!
It is very tall, too.
Look how small the people are!
And it is as heavy as five cars!
Now it is walking.
It is walking on two big legs.
Look at its big feet!
Each foot has three big toes.
Scientists think a T. rex made this footprint.
Now it is opening its mouth.
Look at its teeth!
Its biggest teeth are longer than a banana!
They are very sharp!
Chomp!
It has a super strong bite.
It can even crunch bones!
Now look at its arms.
Its arms are so tiny!
Each hand has just two fingers.
But it has a big nose.
It can smell food from far away!
Sniff, sniff!
Now it is hunting.
Look!
It is grabbing a Triceratops!
Today, we can see its bones.
This is Sue, a famous T. rex.
Sue is in a big museum in Chicago.
Let's say the words!
T. rex!
Dinosaur!
Big!
Tall!
Heavy!
Walk!
Teeth!
Sharp!
Bite!
Arms!
Nose!
Bones!
Museum!
Great job!
Bye-bye, T. rex!
Oh!
It is opening its mouth!
It is only yawning!
See you next time!